Here comes Vernon Roth from Westcliffe,
Colorado, which is one of the most
beautiful towns I've ever experienced.
He's a professional researcher.
He's gone into ancient technology and
languages, very, very deep knowledge.
He's worked with alternative technology
in medical areas. He got into this
basically to help heal his daughter, and
he just ran with it, and he's built up
some amazing
material in the past few years. He's
working to make ideal technology into
real-world technology.
He's also studied codes in the Bible,
different types of research like that.
And he says the one thing that's helped
him, and this might be a clue for some
of us.
One thing that's helped him with his
research is he processes knowledge as
patterns and movements.
And that's a very, very interesting way
to go at it. So, here's Vernon Roth.
Uh good afternoon, everyone.
Um I put this up instead of an
introductory page because
in a lot of our research, we have found
that shapes and
um patterns affect how your mind works.
And I wanted to set a certain tone with
with what we're talking about here
today. And this is a picture by a friend
of mine. It's original artwork, and it's
it's it's absolutely quite beautiful. It
actually portrays the spiral patterns
that come out of black holes, um and
I'll talk about the references. It's it
portrays the energy that flows out of
black holes and actually permeates the
earth as the earth moves through the
universe and
excuse me, and rotates this energy
actually comes down to us and all living
things on the planet. So, I wanted you
to be thinking about that as we started
this this presentation today.
All right.
Now, I've never talked about a
a subject that is really more
controversial or in my opinion more
misunderstood than the Joe Cell
technology. And I wanted to talk about
first off
there aren't a whole lot of people here
that are that are actually doing
research in this. So, I wanted to touch
on
what this is all about real quick before
we go on.
Joe Cell technology was originally
discovered in about the '90s.
Uh
so, about 15 16 years ago. And it was
used to run a car essentially.
What we have is a researcher that found
a way to run a vehicle utilizing a a set
a
excuse me, a set of concentric rings or
set set of concentric tubes
and generated some type of
not physical gas, but an energy that
appeared to run the vehicle.
Now, no I've never been to Australia and
I have never actually seen a vehicle
work on it. But, I got into this
kind of serendipitously
because I was researching energy and
energy and health and had how health
affects the or how energy how affects
the body.
And I was led to the Joe Cell
technology. So, when you go out there
and
shock yourself with our shocking water
on the table, remember that as we were
perfecting this, there were there were
three books on the table. One was
Alex Shiffer's book from Australia on
Joe Cell technology. The next one was
Peter Lindemann's book on cold
electricity and the third one we won't
get into, but
as we
move into this, I want to tell you a
little bit about what why this has been
brought to the forefront right now.
This work was being done in Australia
for a number of years and there wasn't a
huge amount of success with it
until just recently apparently a a
gentleman here in the United States, the
only person that apparently has been
able to make it operate here in the
United States
was actually running his truck on it and
it made a truck his older pickup truck
run
much much differently than it was
designed to. Let's just put it that way.
The information is out there. It's it's
really
um, it's really
out there. And so if you find if if you
want to research this, then please feel
free to go ahead. It's um, it it's
really interesting and will illuminate
the subject greatly. But apparently
as the story goes, he was threatened by
them
and told to cease and desist. And this
has caught a huge amount of interest all
over the world.
Literally there are over a hundred
people here in the United States
dedicating all of their time and
resources to finding out how the Joe
Cell works and why it functioned and why
it was able to run this and why
they
would threaten to shut one person down
for use utilizing this on his car.
And that that that really is really what
we're getting at here is why would why
would somebody stop a person from using
a technology that
very seldom works for anybody else. The
only person in the entire northern
hemisphere that can make it run.
That's what we're going to get into.
What really amazes me about the Joe Cell
is the fact that as I said, there are
over a hundred researchers in the United
States alone right now who are working
with the Joe Cell, who are literally
trying to create
energy from nothing. They want to create
a fuel to run a vehicle
from nothing at all.
There are easier ways to run a vehicle.
There are easier ways to There are
easier ways to generate power. There are
easier ways to
generate fuel. There's Brown's gas.
There's electricity. There's hydrogen.
All of these things are are much easier
ways to do this. Why has it captured the
the minds and attention of all these
researchers? And why are these people so
dedicated to the subject?
Um
I'm going to illustrate why. When I
started working with the with this
technology, a friend of mine came to
visit that I hadn't seen for a number of
years and he just said, "I'm passing
through Colorado. Can I crash at your
place?" I said, "Sure."
And as we're sitting there talking, we
were talking about what we were uh some
of the things that he were we were
doing. He was a massage therapist.
And I he said, "So, uh what have you
been doing?" I I I almost started
saying, "Just wait. I have to tell you
about a dream I had."
He says, "I was in the dream
and I was dreamed I walked into this
museum and this museum was obviously in
the future because fantastically amazing
stuff were be there being displayed as
antiques.
And the entire museum focused down on on
one little spot um in the center of this
museum and there was a little device and
it was a thing that held liquid and it
had magnets in it and it and it
generated energy and and it was what all
technology was based on in the future.
Doesn't that sound like an interesting
dream? And I was scribbling down a rough
diagram of what I was working on and
said, uh "Joseph, does it look like
that?" And he said, "Oh, yeah. What is
that?"
This is why
This is why it has captured the minds of
all these people. It is like a new quest
for the Holy Grail. And we'll be talking
about the Holy Grail a little bit later
on, but it is literally
the energy of the future.
Okay?
All right. So, are we ready to begin the
new quest Oops. Are we ready to begin
the new quest for the Holy Grail?
Yes. Okay. Let's go on.
Okay.
All right. What is a Joe Cell?
Now, if you look it up online, you will
find the descriptions. You will find the
stainless steel rings, tubes separated
by spacers. This is a mechanism.
The Joe Cell
if we
Excuse me. If we examine
My stuff is not coming up.
It's okay.
If we examine what it is, it is
five or six concentric tubes of steel,
of paramagnetic steel.
They're separated by spacers, which are
diamagnetic spacers,
and they have liquid water in the center
of it.
So, and when you apply an electrical
current to this, you have a magnetic
field that is generated going through
the
Excuse me. Going through the cell. As I
said, this is the mechanism. This is a
means to
How do I make my pictures appear or my
words?
Oh, there we go. I have to hit the other
button.
All right. It is literally a means to
harness energy. That is what a Joe Cell
is.
When we When we run up against a brick
wall, and we can no longer move any
further forward, we have to start
examining why we were moving in the
first place.
When we were working with this, there
are a number of situations many times
where we ran where where where we would
discover something completely
serendipitously. We would discover
an amazing process or a an amazing
technique that that took us leaps and
bounds from where we were. And then
suddenly,
we'd hit a brick wall and couldn't go
any further.
And we discovered that that those leaps
and bounds that we had just just gone
through were just the the initial
stages, the like the birth pains of
discovering this. Then we have to go
back to the very beginning and say, "Why
did it work in the first place?" So,
that's what we're going to do with the
Joe Cell here today.
Excuse me.
The Joe Cell is a means to harness
energy.
And
there's a big debate about what type of
energy. And I I don't want to go into
hydrinos and and all of the wonderful
technical terms that people have applied
to this because it really is confusing.
I I don't care about it. Um
because I operate on a certain
on a certain approach to to reality. I
believe in something called
etheric light.
Um and this is supported by a number of
researchers, but I operate on the belief
that there is etheric light. It is a
tangible substance that we can utilize
if we have the right tools to do so.
Now, last year when I gave my
presentation, I started it out with the
statement that the establishment will
never discover Sorry. The establishment
will never discover free energy
as long as they believe that free energy
is not possible to discover.
So, by believing and accepting the fact
that there is etheric light
that I can utilize it
with different devices, then I can use
then I really can use that and utilize
it. I'll leave it to the mathematicians
and the physicists later on to figure
out the mathematics of it, to figure out
the formulas, to to
it. Right now, I'm going to use it and
I'm going to talk about how everyone can
use it.
So,
let us move on.
Now, I've given everybody a little
handout with um if you didn't get one,
there may be some still in the box.
Uh
these are rough outlines of the of the
slides and uh you can take notes on it
if you're going to be constructing cells
or if you want to think about
constructing um or utilizing this type
of technology. It's a good reference
sheet to uh to go from, good base to
start from, and then you can read the
rest of the books and uh that are out
there and and and have a little bit
different understanding about what's
happening.
Okay. So, we have our energy we are
going to be utilizing is etheric light.
So, first of all, we have to understand
how we're going to trap it.
How we're going to trap etheric light.
This thing's weird.
Please uh bear with me here.
All right.
Moving right along.
Uh references, I have a list of
references at the end of the at the end
of the presentation that you can all
copy down. I sorry, they did not get
onto the handout. Um
so, don't worry about the references
that as we're going through here.
We create We capture etheric light by
creating an environment
by creating an environment, structure,
or antenna that allows and encourages a
continual flow of the ether.
This is a picture
of a Peter Stevens style Joe Cell.
Uh see oh see um
this is concentric rings of
paramagnetic steel separated by
what should be diamagnetic spacers
filled with water inside of a glass
isolation
bottle uh vessel. Okay?
A Joe Cell is going
as I said, going to allow and encourage
the continual flow of ether or etheric
light
and it's going to do this using water,
shape, and resonance. And we're going to
discuss each one of those
and and how to utilize those. And then
and we'll and I have examples up here on
the table.
So,
here we go.
All right.
Why do we use water, first off?
As uh Dan Davidson said in his uh
lecture presentation uh 2 years ago,
water, or excuse me, ether, I did the
exact same the thing that he did.
Ether is hydroscopic. Ether is attracted
to water. Ether wants to go to water. As
a matter of fact, I have a friend who
just proposed a theory. He's been
studying this uh almost as long as I
have. He just proposed a theory just a
recently. He said, "What if, just
imagine for a minute, that all life on
this planet is in fact a
a pattern that was developed, an
interference pattern that was developed
by the etheric energy interacting with
the water on this planet?"
Interesting idea.
So,
we're going to use water because ether
is hydroscopic. This also explains why
the ocean is a huge concentration
point for etheric elements. Uh I talked
last year about uh
high spin or high energy elements that
that do not show up normally on uh on
regular spectrographs and such. Um
the highest concentrations of these are
in oceans or in uh places that used to
be oceans. Uh
uh what are now deserts or uh um
or glaciers.
The The next reason why we're going to
use water is it's very easy to
manipulate the nature of water. And as
we've seen already with uh some of the
other speakers, uh water is actually
starting to come into the consciousness
of people as being more important than
just something that we're going to
hydrate with, which reminds me I'm
getting dry.
So,
and the third reason that we are going
to
excuse me.
Use water is that once you manipulate
the water, you manipulate its effects.
And we've already had a speaker actually
speak about
um
I do that Masaru Emoto
and his photographs
of crystalline structures in water. And
we know that
if you simply stick a label onto water
with a word on it,
the water will pick up the frequency of
that word. Well, further research
actually found that it was not the label
that went onto the water. It wasn't the
word actually, it was the emotion. It
was the emotional content of the person
that put it there.
So,
excuse me.
Words Words are interchangeable. They
are labels. They are manifestations of
our thought consciousness.
What What our emotions do is they go out
into our reality and affect the reality
as evidenced by these by these
photographs.
This is another way to manipulate water.
I put it in there because I find it very
beautiful, but also take a look at the
spacings there.
You see
spacing narrow, spacing slightly larger
larger, spacing slightly larger, all
ratios of how wide
the water the waterfall is to its fall
rate.
Now, does that look
uh whoops, wrong way.
Does that look at all similar to that
right there?
These are patterns that we have to dis
that we have to start noticing.
Patterns are how we are are are how we
interact with reality.
Okay? We move through traffic by
watching the pattern the flow or at
least we should by watching the pattern
and flow of the cars around us. So, we
watch for patterns.
So, as we're talking about water,
there are three different ways to
manipulate water uh that that I I've
that I I consider.
Um they're chemically,
alchemically, and mechanically. And
we're going to talk about each one of
those.
Let's see here. Am I missing something?
All right, I want to uh really quickly
go back to just uh
really quickly go back to something. On
your page, I have uh I've down in the
center of the second page, I have down
um
what can kill a cell.
Now, there are stories out there about
utilizing these cells,
and
they are really contingent upon the
they're really contingent upon the
mindset of the person that's using the
cell.
And so, and so there there are these
stories about people driving the car and
saying a single word, and
the the the the vehicle dying because it
was running on the cell. There are
people that talk about charging their
cell, and we'll get into that. We'll get
into all of that. Um for the people that
don't know about that, we will we will
get there. There are people that talk
about charging their cell, and if
something happens, the cell will die,
and they have to dump the water out and
start all over again.
There are a couple of things that will
What's that?
What?
Oh.
Oh, thank you. I appreciate that. All
right. Um there are a couple of things
that are going to kill a cell.
One is anger.
Anger will kill a cell.
We have been operating machine,
charging the water that you see out
there. Someone comes into the room with
a
just uh
they were angry at the world, they hated
their mother, they were
uh not really happy with life, and we
watched the power levels literally, we
had a meter, watch the power levels
and we could charge a bottle all day
long and it would not shock you.
Had to tear apart the machine, rebuild
it, put it back together again with the
right attitude and boom, there it goes.
So, that is an absolute God's honest
truth.
Another way to kill a water.
Excuse me.
Um
I'll just get right to it. Uh we were
working and we could charge
500 bottles of water before we had to
go to the before we had to recycle and
uh and start all over again.
And we stopped working with uh certain
people and we were suddenly able to
charge over 1,000 bottles of water.
What was the difference?
The difference was that the people we
were working with were addicted to
pornography.
Yeah.
So, we were immediately able to start
charging vast amounts of water by not
working with them. It really perturbed
me. People on the Joe Cell uh groups
will remember this. It really perturbed
me when someone was talking about,
"Yeah, I can get to stage three B by
watching porn with my cell, but I can't
seem to get beyond that."
There's a reason why.
Because water is etheric. Water
is filled with ether energy.
And there are certain things that ether
energy just doesn't like.
Okay, let's get on to
Thank you, I appreciate that. Um let's
get on to chemical changes in water.
All right.
It's kind of funny, when I read on the
Joe Cell groups, the people talk about
Oops, sorry. People talk about um
I'm using this type of water, I'm using
that type of water and they're all using
horrible, horrible water. They're using
distilled water that they buy in the
store, which is leaching plasticine out
of the milk carton jugs that they put
distilled water into
or they are using city water and they
can't understand why they get this green
scum when they're working with their
water or this brown stuff at the bottom
of their at the bottom of their chamber.
The original research on on the on a Joe
Cell was done with beautiful mountain
spring water or well, beautiful spring
water.
And we will get to that later because
there's a connection. Just put that
click set that on the shelf and remember
that.
Okay?
As you can see,
there's chlorine.
Uh some cities are now using hydrogen
peroxide instead of chlorine. It's it's
a good thing. It's still not not
fantastic. Uh there's fluoride which
we love fluoride, right? It's good for
our teeth.
Um
Yeah, I uh
I I I debated talking about this, but
fluoride was what they put into the
water at Dachau and Auschwitz to keep
the Jews from rebelling in the in the in
the
prison camps. That's why a handful of
people could guard hundreds, maybe a
thousand thousands of people because
those people were so doped up, they
couldn't even think about rebelling
against those guys.
Could have overwhelmed them by sheer
numbers.
But they had fluoride in their water and
their brains had turned to mush.
Get a water filter.
I live in the mountains with beautiful
spring water. It's interesting because
when I come down and work with certain
people in town,
some sometimes their brains are right
on, sometimes they're just
because they're they just drink right
out of the tap water.
Water filters, British Berkefeld water
filters, my personal favorite, are the
best. But anyway,
that's uh blackberkey.com, by the way.
Um
All of these things all of these
chemicals that go into our water change
the crystalline structure. And we'll be
talking about crystalline structure as I
get into some of these
these items here on the table.
Um all of these chemicals change the
crystalline structure of water
to something that is not beneficial to
the body. And so, I wanted to touch real
quick on on a on a method that is really
phenomenal for for getting rid of
uh those chemicals as well as changing
the crystalline structure back. This
uh
is an interesting device. It's found on
subtleenergies.com.
Once again, that'll be at the end of the
lecture on a screen.
Um subtleenergies.com.
This is an ozone generator. It does not
It is not your ozone generator that you
drop into your hot tub. It is an ozone
generator that generates O17 at a at an
insanely high um
electrostatic voltage.
It is bubbled through a tank. And by the
way, this is mine waste that they were
originally treating.
Um this mine waste was from Litchfield.
They were literally uh
had arsenic and all sorts of fun
chemicals in it. The water from the from
the mine waste would flow down through
here. They would bubble it through these
bubblers. Now, it's interesting because
when
you use this type of ozone,
there is literally a vortex created
because the the electrostatic pressure
through the ozone is so high that it
literally moves into a vortex.
The water would then flow out here and
into a big huge vat of charcoal
briquettes, into a drain tank, and flow
off. Now, for all the free energy
researchers out here, here's a great
one. There's a little grounding rod
there.
What they found was that this this rod
or excuse me, this this wire would
disintegrate. They had a little 12-gauge
wire. It disintegrated. Burned up. So,
they replaced it with an 8-gauge wire.
And that burned up, and they replaced it
with a 6-gauge wire. And that burned up,
and they eventually got down to a wire
the size of my thumb, and it got hot
because of all of the electrostatics
that the ozone interacting with the
particulates that were flowing through
that water tank, it was generating
energy. And they had to ground it. They
were just cycling this stuff to ground.
Um
there's there's something going on here.
There there's even more going on here.
This this stack of briquettes of of
activated charcoal literally yielded
more gold and platinum group metals than
the mine was producing itself. But we
won't go into that.
All righty then. This is developed by a
gentleman and his story is on
subtleenergies.com. Please please read
it because it will help you in all of
your research whether you're researching
carbon arcs, Tesla research, Joe Cell
water treatment, whatever.
So, ozone of the right type is very
good. Ozone of the wrong type is bad.
And the other thing is I have to say
this,
if you are bubbling ozone into your
house to kill bacteria, one of the
foremost researchers in the medical
community has found that of ozone has
found that the the safest way to do it
is to bubble it through a bottle of
olive oil.
And instead of just bubbling it out into
the air, you cannot smell the ozone but
it still kills the bacteria and it's
much more healthy for the human body.
Because ozone is it is a killer. It goes
in. But when you bubble it through the
olive oil, it's it's it's much more
effective. I just had to say that.
Uh was there a question someplace? Does
it need to be extra virgin? What's that?
Does it need to be extra virgin olive
oil?
Extra virgin olive oil is the best, yes.
Cold pressed?
Well, I don't know.
I actually I do use cold pressed but
that's okay.
Um
Okay, let's move on.
Another way to to effect a change in
water chemically is through the use of
the study of Ormus. Now, Ormus I was my
actual presentation last year. It is
high energy high spin monoatomic or
diatomic structurally rearranged atoms.
They do not for they do not show up as
regular metals when you look at them
under an x-ray spectrograph or in in an
x-ray spectrograph. For instance, gold
in an Ormus state is actually either
white powder or a golden glass instead
of a metal.
It There are There are many things. It's
too It's It's I could
lecture for 3 days on that.
subtleenergies.com is the website to
go with. Excuse me.
This is what my original lecture was on.
This is a picture of of
of gold that has formed inside of glass.
And they started out with glass. They
have literally
manifested, created gold in a microwave
of all things utilizing nothing but
glass as an input. Okay? So, this is the
first real uh
uh or one of one of the most real and
tangible evidences that yes,
um you can manifest metals and you can
manifest things that were not there to
begin with.
Let's see. Where are we? Okay, so I
There's a There's a huge study in this,
but what's really important is that we
use lye to cause pH swings in the
seawater or in the different types of
water that we'll discuss later on. We
use lye to cause pH swings. And when we
swing the pH, we take it down to a very
low pH and then bring it back up slowly.
Uh for Joe Cell researchers is is
exactly the same way as you utilize a
Joe Cell. Uh you have different you have
pHs and you go through a pH pattern
inside of the cell. So, that's a huge
subject to talk about and I I won't get
into that uh very much right now.
But, it's a great field to study if
you're studying anything from like I
said Tesla research to longevity.
Moving right along, and I seem to have
lost the picture, but
oh, well.
Okay, we're now moving on to alchemical
changes. Now, I I included the Ormus
right before alchemical because the
Ormus utilizes chemicals, but it is also
an alchemical change to water. Alchemy,
in my definition,
is in fact a an endothermic implosive
action. When you study alchemy, and I've
been studying this recently, it's a
fantastic field. It's really fun, really
confusing, but hey, it's part of the
adventure, right? Um all alchemical
processes are implosive. They focus
their energy inward. They are
endothermic actions, okay? They are not
chemical reactions. So, this mimics our
natural environment. This actually
mimics our world.
Um
our Earth's natural forces. If you were
to go to, let's say, Hawaii and study
black smokers, which are essentially
small volcanoes under the water, you
would find that the heat inside of these
things is is absolutely tremendous. And
there's they're boiling the water right
there. But you go
5 or 10 ft away underwater, and the heat
drops off completely. All of the heat is
implosive. It is endothermic. Exactly
like what happens in a Brown's gas.
Larry was demonstrating it earlier
today. He's vaporizing tungsten
and just completely destroying it.
Brown's gas indexing itself to whatever
you put it against and destroys it. And
yet he's holding on to the tip of the
the tip of the torch. It's not burning
him. And it to actually measure it, the
air around the Brown's gas flame is only
like 270°.
It's implosive action. It's going
inward. All All alchemical formulas are
like that.
So, this this brought brings up another
subject. I I love this subject, and
anyone who knows me knows I cannot talk
for very long without going here, is is
is the ancient is the ancient
technologies.
Boy, I tell you that that's a fantastic
field to study. As a matter of fact, if
you're if you're researching along, it
doesn't matter what you're researching,
if you're researching along and you hit
a brick wall and you cannot go any
further,
pick up a mythology book.
Pick up the Bible.
Pick up anything that that has nothing
to do with what you're reading.
Pick up something that will talk about
what is done anciently, how they lived
anciently, and you will start to
train your mind to look in new places
for answers and you'll start finding
answers. Mythology books, they're like
they're like textbooks. Uh excuse me,
they're like scientific textbooks.
It's fantastic. When we start looking
into the ancients, we start finding
interesting things like the Baghdad
Battery.
Now, what is very interesting uh with
this uh with this battery that they
found and they found many of these uh
since the original discovery of the
Baghdad Battery. Um
what they have found is that this area,
right here, this area was completely
empty. This was um
just air, okay? It was sealed with wax
and bitumen, which is uh sealed with
asphalt essentially.
It's a rod
and a
and a vessel sealed at the bottom,
filled with acid, and it generated 1 V
of electricity. Now,
uh
MythBusters did one on this. They said,
"1 V of electricity, what could they do
with that?" That's is debunked and uh
it's a myth. Well, 1 V of electricity
that's somewhere around 10 amps. You
start putting those with a lot of them,
what can you do? And Joe Cell
researchers, you will automatically you
you can keep a Joe Cell alive, remember,
using 1 V of electricity on a leaky
cell. So, what can't you do with one of
these little things about this big right
here with a Joe Cell. But, what's real
more important is the shape.
It's the actual shape.
And when you study ancient alchemy, when
you study uh
when you study alchemical formulas,
you find references to something called
the anaphor, as you see there.
And this is essentially the same size as
an anaphor. This is a Phi harmonically
tuned vessel
that is it's absolutely amazing. They
would literally create reactions inside
one of these that would become red hot,
white hot,
and become so hot that this would become
transparent, and you could see the
reaction going on inside.
Now, this is not a myth. We have done
this. We have done this recently. It's
become so hot, it wasn't in this, it was
in something else entirely, but it
literally you could literally see the
action inside, but there was no heat
escaping, and the vessel held its shape.
All because of the shape of the vessel.
So, it's interesting that the Hindus
would say that the universe is an egg.
Okay? The universe is an egg in which we
are constantly moving and traveling
through.
So, this was a this is basically uh an
an anaphor, a small uh
excuse me, a small anaphor. They had
much larger ones. This is very
interesting because if you were to boil
this is specially designed that if you
were to pour boiling water into this
vessel, in just a few minutes, it would
be ice cold.
Just because of the vortex. Another
gentleman was uh standing up here. I I
really appreciate you telling me about
this because he was standing here and he
said, "Th- This is amazing. This This is
one of the most effective etheric energy
accumulators, all based on the shape
that it's in, right here."
So,
I hope we're getting some I hope we're
we're getting some clues here as to why
the why the Joe Cell functions um the
way it does, this by the way is the
modern version of the anaphor. Kind of
looks kind of ugly. That's titanium by
the way. We have to use titanium now
because we don't understand the shape.
We don't understand the reactions that
are going on there. Titanium's the only
thing that will actually contain the
reaction cuz it'll boil through steel
and all that fun stuff. So, that's
that's an anaphor now. It's it it
doesn't do what it's supposed to do it
doesn't
it because it doesn't have the shape
anymore. Okay?
We
We lose something as we as in our in our
high-tech world. We believe that we've
got all the answers. And I could just I
could go on for that for a long time.
But, we won't. So, we're going to move
on. Next thing that we're going to talk
about al- and with alchemical changes to
water is lightning.
Now, in our research into ancient
techniques for transformation not of
elements but actually well, elements too
but actually the human body. In our
research into immortality,
I love that. I love that word. Um
we find references to lots and lots of
lightning rods. Down here you will see a
picture of both of a Minoan temple that
existed high in the mountains of of of
uh
uh the Minoan civilization was on Crete.
Excuse me.
These right here are lightning rods.
Now, why would a temple want to attract
lightning? Lightning kills people.
Well, they were doing it for a very
specific reason. Uh interestingly
enough, these are exactly the same type
as are same same
shape as the lightning rods that Ben
Franklin told people to put up to keep
themselves from getting struck by
lightning. Exact same shape. We just you
know, we're now using it uh
a lot
3,000 years later.
Great.
Everything old is new again.
All right. Um Joe Blankenship was here.
Uh I don't know if he's Is that you up
there, Joe?
Okay, great. Joe Blankenship
um, sometime talked to him about the
chamber in the Grand Canyon.
Uh, we found a temple
down in uh, Southern Utah
that used to exist on a lake. The uh,
supplicants would row up to this uh,
temple and park their boats. We found a
dock. We found the steps that they walk
up to.
Um, all of these things have in common
is that they all used lightning for some
purpose.
And we we came to understand why, but
our our real confirmation was when a
friend of mine
um,
gave me an excerpt from the unpublished
uh, book the whole or the unavailable
book the Holy Trinity Sophia by the
saint by the alchemist Saint Germain.
And one of the stages to uh, immortality
was to bathe in water struck by
lightning.
What's interesting is what type of
water. He makes a very distinct um,
statement that it must be beautiful
mountain spring water or blue glacial
water.
Literally, I'll just jump to the end
here. Literally, they were utilizing the
lightning
even in this chamber inside of a inside
of a mountain in the Grand Canyon.
They're utilizing the lightning to
affect a change in the water. An
implosive reaction or an implosive
action on the water. And it affected the
body that was saturated with it.
Okay? So, water in a cell is very
important. You cannot use
tap water. You cannot use deionized
water out of the store. You cannot use
distilled water. You must find a good
water source. And I'll be talking about
how to make your own water to do that.
You must find a good water source. And
you guys, if you're never going to run a
car on it, that's fine. I'm going to
tell you all sorts of other uses for a
Joe cell in our in our lecture, just
just so you know. So, you're not saying,
well, this doesn't apply to me. So,
anyway, let's see if I skipped anything
on this one.
Okay. Moving right along.
Oh, uh those hieroglyphs are from the uh
temple south of here in the uh
in the uh uh that used to be on a lake.
It's in the the uh um mountains south of
here. I'm not going to tell anyone where
they are. I'm sorry.
Uh
It was interesting um
these are some of the few remaining
hieroglyphs that were there the last
time we went there. It's on private
property. The last time we went there um
literally my sister and I were crawling
around underneath these cliff faces
taking pictures of the few remaining
hieroglyphs and places in this temple
site because the owners were literally
standing up on the cliff ledge talking
about how they wanted to uh destroy the
rest of the pictograms so people would
stop coming on their property.
So, um
these are some of the few remaining
ones. There used to be hundreds. Uh over
the past several years they've all been
destroyed except for these and and a few
others. Um this literally talks about a
vessel, a chamber.
That's a symbol for gold. It is also the
symbol for light or the sun
giving you through birth or excuse me,
through burial it resurrection eternal
life. Um there's more to it than that.
You can actually read these petroglyphs
five different ways at least that we've
documented. A spiritual, a social uh uh
a social, uh a scientific
so and and alchemical actually we've
discovered. So, there's at least four or
five different ways to read these
writings that all make sense
um and you can apply to any one of the
writings. But, it's absolutely
beautiful. We were um able I said this
last year, but I'll say it again. We
were actually able to go in the middle
of the night. A friend of mine and I got
on uh went to this place and we drank of
this water that that we now make now
that we learned how to make from this
whole temple site. Um we drank that at
the very spot that the initiates used to
drink drink it 4,000 years ago. It was
amazing experience, very beautiful, but
very spiritual. Uh that by the way is my
daughter. She wants to grow up to be
Laura Croft.
I'm fostering this because she will
discover things that that we have just
not even dreamed of.
So moving right along.
Excuse me.
Another thing that we start to find when
we uh when we research uh uh
uh Joe Cell technology, and I'm just
going to borrow uh this one right here.
This is by a gentleman This is developed
by a gentleman in the in the audience
and it's a great illustration. I do not
use this style, so I didn't have one to
bring.
This is These are concentric rings of
steel.
Paramagnetic steel.
Separated by spacers.
And when we start studying Joe Cell
technology,
we find that the Joe Cells have to be
shiny.
They have to be diamagnetic.
And
Excuse me. There is something else that
we all should be acquainted with that is
exactly the same way and that is cloud
busters. Now originally we all think of
cloud busters as being concentric or
excuse me grouped tubes.
But what's interesting is that those
tubes have to be phi harmonically
balanced by length to width. They all
have to They have to have certain ratios
that you utilize them in. And the
original
um the original cloud busters were not
grouped tubes. They looked more like
that
with spirals in them.
And the variations on that. You can
actually make a cloud buster exactly
like you make that if you make it phi
harmonically balanced to length and
widths. And they are incredibly
effective. Uh they can do amazing
things. There is a gentleman in in the
audience. Um
you know what? I'll talk to him later. I
don't know if he wants that brought up.
But anyway, um
So, Joe Cell uh can we have the picture?
Thank you. Um Joe Cell technology
relates to Cloudbusters because we have
the shiny concentric or grouped pipes.
Once again, they are also diamagnetic
versus paramagnetic. We have a
paramagnetic metal. Oh, and by the way,
I need to define those terms. I I
apologize. Um
In in uh
before we had the current table of
elements, we used to divide up our our
elements into three groups. We had
magnetic elements over here. Or excuse
me, we had diamagnetic elements over
here, which were elements that were
negatively affected by uh by magnetic
fields. They tried to move away from any
magnetic field. So, the most the most
diamagnetic element is bismuth. And that
is really fun to play with. If you I
mean, you could devote months and months
and months of study to bismuth. Bismuth
is um bismuth literally converts heat
differentials into energy. Uh literally
power. Um there are many applications
for that. It We have differentials all
around us. We We have uh heat
differentials. We have all sorts of
differentials. Bismuth converts that
into energy. So, bismuth is the the most
diamagnetic element that there is. So,
we have diamagnetic elements over here.
We had paramagnetic elements over here.
Paramagnetic, I believe, and someone
correct me if I'm wrong, paramagnetic
elements are elements that do not
respond to a magnetic field unless they
are under excuse me, under an electrical
impulse or an under electrical uh
current.
And then we had magnetic materials in
the center. This is how it used to be
divided up. And what's interesting is
this was before they discovered the the
uh
the um
noble gases. The noble gases then go
right click click click click click
right into the center between the
diamagnetic, the paramagnetic, and the
magnetic elements.
So, those are the those are some
definitions for you for for paramagnetic
versus diamagnetic. We are paramagnetic
beings.
It's interesting. Concrete that we walk
on all day long
is diamagnetic.
You put a paramagnetic shield between
you and the concrete, suddenly you have
increased energy.
Um if you were to set a battery on
concrete, the very crystalline structure
of the diamagnetic concrete would suck
the life right out of the battery. Same
exact thing happens with the water. If
you set the water on concrete, they just
suck it right out because it is the
antithesis of what we ourselves need to
operate at. So, and then we go out and
we build buildings out of
diamagnetic material. Kind of
defeats the purpose of life, doesn't it?
Okay, so now we've got a definition for
paramagnetic versus diamagnetic. And
you'll notice in your handout I have it
in many places. I cannot stress enough
paramagnetics versus diamagnetics, okay?
The other interesting thing about just
Okay, so
cloudbusters, we have a we have a metal
here. We have a dissimilar You can't see
it, but we have a dissimilar metal
inside of resin down in the bottom. So,
we have a differential once again. We
have a differential between the metal of
the pipes and the metal inside of the
inside of the bucket. And so, when these
are properly utilized,
grounded into water or um Excuse me,
specifically into you need to have it
into flowing water because if you ground
it into regular water, assuming if you
ground it into standing water, it will
corrupt it with the with the energy that
it that it's cleaning out of the skies.
So, flowing water works best,
but it will cause an etheric draw.
And there are people that say, "Well,
it's not etheric. It's it's ionics and
there's there's ion flow." And And no,
we we've done experiments where we
literally caused a an etheric cascade
and Mother Nature tried to breach the
hole in a very violent manner
uh using one of these one of those and
another machine.
Um
so it is literally ether energy and it
is flowing this way and ether energy
that is flowing with from a
powered by cloud buster is pulling
everything with it so it's pulling all
of the the uh
the toxins out of the air and that's why
it cleans the atmosphere or one of the
reasons why.
Um
so think about this this grounded to
into water to actually that should not
say collect I apologize that should say
to
eliminate the energy. So gel cell people
that cell has to be completely isolated
from the metal of your car, okay?
Because otherwise all of the etheric
energy that you are actually producing
all of the etheric energy that you're
actually drawing is just getting
grounded out into the metal of your
vehicle, okay?
The problem is that we're still plugging
it into the negative pole of the the
alternator and that's grounding it out
too because the negative pole is still
ground is connected to the chassis of
your car, okay? Just FYI.
All righty then.
Oops, thank you.
All right, there is a connection here
and I love this I love this connection
because like I said I study ancient
ancient archaeology and such. This is a
work done by Phil Callahan and I know
that Joe Blankenship has brought this up
several times.
Phil Callahan is a genius. He's an
absolute genius. If you ever find Dr.
Phil Callahan's works pick every single
one of them up you can pay as much as
you can. Um when he dies
the world will have lost one of the most
brilliant minds that there is, okay? So
study his works. He documented that the
ancient Irish towers a connection
between the ancient Irish towers and the
Egyptian obelisks.
These were paramagnetic material, and
this is a picture of one.
These were paramagnetic materials
that formed into a specific shape
started to affect that they would
actually affect magnets. Um and I'll
I'll I'll uh talk about that in just a
second here.
But they would affect the air around
these and the ground exactly like a
cloudbuster does. It would literally
clean the air, and these were put up
before the pollution and such. So
literally it would energize the ground
with a positive life force energy, and
the ground around these would just
thrive. And in Egypt, there are no
Egyptian obelisks where they are
originally.
Nearly every single Egyptian obelisk has
been moved sometime between the time it
was put up and now, and most of that
happened within the last 200 years,
okay?
There are no Egyptian obelisks that are
even standing exactly the same way that
they were. All of the Egyptian obelisks
that exist now are standing on some type
of firm foundation, whereas originally
they were standing on a foundation of
their same type of material in a way
Oops, can I go back? In a way that
grounded them out. Nope, it's the wrong
way.
Um just like a cloudbuster had to be.
These Egyptian
These Egyptian obelisks while not
affecting so much rain, they would
literally affect the ground and allow
these plants to grow because it effuses
the ground with paramagnetic energy.
Okay?
So we So once again, we're coming back
to paramagnetic versus diamagnetic.
We're running into differentials in
energy. Where Where does that uh
Think about that. Think about where that
is going to take us.
What we What else we find with Dr. Phil
Callahan's work is something really
astounding. And this is
uh this is worth every single penny,
every single one of you paid to get into
this lecture, okay? And I've talked to a
few people
and told them about this, but I'm going
to tell it to everybody now because
everybody needs to understand this. Um
and you may not understand the
implications of this for a long time,
but but listen to what I'm about to say.
Paramagnetic materials change based on
geometric structure alone.
So,
Oh, I got to tell you this neat little
story.
I learned about this, read the book.
The very next day, the very next day, I
took my daughter, uh Sage, the one in
the picture, to
uh the science museum up in Denver.
And we were waiting in line to get into
the science museum. She loves it. She
goes to see the Egyptian display. She
likes to see the Native American
displays.
Uh really fun stuff. We're waiting in
line and there was this little kid,
about this big,
waiting in line with his family in front
of us. And he is standing there with I
kid you not this in his hand with little
fins
off of it as a rocket ship.
I said, "Wait a minute, that you know, I
catch you out of the corner of my eye."
I said, "Wait a minute, that looks
really familiar." And this kid is flying
it around.
And I look at it
and it this one isn't even a completely
accurate His little rocket ship even had
the windows of this tower in it.
And I knew right then
I knew right then that I was being led
to an answer about paramagnetism.
That night I learned about magnetic uh
magnetic resonance and the importance of
magnetic resonance in our lives. Uh
I I I we haven't figured out exactly
everything about it, so I'm not going to
talk about it, but but think about that
in in life, magnetic resonance. That
little boy was like almost like a a
serendipitous messenger saying, "You're
on the right track. Go with it." So,
let's see if I'm missing anything. Any
questions about this so far?
Now, where are our rockets then
currently in the air?
I have seen convincing evidence in the
past 6 months that um you remember Jules
Verne?
Jules Verne wrote um
From the Earth to the Moon way, way back
when.
He had uh pinpointed Cape Canaveral to
within I think it was 50 mi. He knew
exactly where our new almost exactly
where Cape Canaveral would be. He even
had a launch trajectory.
And this is the 1800s.
Um I've seen convincing evidence
mathematical formula that says, "We
launch at that spot to get at a specific
time to get our rockets into a specific
spot that then levitates it out of the
orbit."
Or out into orbit.
So,
um
and I'll get into Leedskalnin, too.
Leedskalnin talks about rocket ships and
how to and how to
go into space, but it all it does it
comes back to paramagnetism and
diamagnetism. If we understood that
paramagnetism and diamag- the the
principles of that, we could literally
have a have a device that resonated so
much paramagnetic energy that it would
launch itself away from the Earth.
Because remember
uh excuse me, not paramag- diamagnetic
energy. Because remember I said
diamagnetics repel away from any pole of
the magnet. And so, if you had a device
that was supercharged with diamagnetic
energy, it would literally just launch
into into space because it's trying to
get away from the Earth.
And then, theoretically, if you could
resonate it with the paramagnetic energy
of the Earth, you could draw it back no
matter where it went in the universe.
But those are that's all speculation.
Anyway, Define dia and para, please.
Diamagnetic and paramagnetic again?
What do they mean?
Okay.
Um paramagnetic
is
steel
for instance for example steel that is
not magnetic in and of itself. It will
not stick to a magnet and yet
um if you put a a current across it then
it be then it will become magnetic just
like a just like a piece of cop- just
like a copper winding, okay?
Um paramagnetic is materials that will
that if this was a magnet it will move
away from a magnet.
I said a diamag- Thank you. I apologize.
Um diamagnetic. So, here's the secret.
Paramagnetic materials change based on
geometrical structure. This
is a piece of sandpaper. No magnet will
stick to it and yet if I were to suspend
it by a string and move a magnet close
to it it would move towards it based on
its geometrical structure alone.
Okay?
This happens on a macrocosmic scale with
this with that tower. It also happens on
a macrocosmic scale if you're to study
bismuth you would
I I can't tell you about the studies in
that, but I can tell you that study it
and you will discover that magnetism,
paramagnetism, conductivity, and this is
in your notes, conductivity and
superconductivity
all are contingent on the geometrical
structure of the element that you're
working with. Okay?
Uh bismuth turns heat into heat and cold
into energy based on its structure.
A superconductor
will conduct energy based on its crystal
and structure. A magnet is a a because
of its crystal and structure. You take
away its crystalline structure, it's no
longer a magnet. You give it back its
crystalline structure, it's a magnet.
Okay? This is one of the most important
things that you'll ever realize if
you're going to build a magnetic motor,
if you're going to uh build something
that's going to energize your yard, it's
all comes back to geometrical patterns.
Okay?
Our thoughts are geometrical patterns.
Remember how I said I put up that
picture at the very beginning and said I
wanted I want to imprint everybody with
a with a thought pattern, okay?
Literally, that thought pattern, that
thought in your mind is going around
creating a geometrical pattern in your
thoughts and your in your head. Yes? Is
it similar to chemical reactions then?
Yes, chemical chemical reactions are
also geometrical patterns, too. And I'm
go I I I I should have brought that up
then. As we change the the uh as we
change as we input chemicals, we add
more and more complex patterns to our
water, and that is what causes the uh
that's what causes the the harmful side
effects of water. I will show you um in
a little bit uh water that is so high pH
it would be like drinking lye and and
yet I can put it on my hands and splash
it on my face because the geometrical
pattern is not such that it would
destroy me. The geometrical pattern is
such that it actually is beneficial to
me. Okay?
It all comes back to patterns. It all
comes back to how things move in the
universe. Yes, sir? Uh what might be
helpful is to refer to it as a
non-ferrous magnetism.
Okay, that works. Well, because a lot of
people think of magnets, they think of
iron.
Yes? And I bought this Dover book on
magnetism and it helped
me to understand
that there were these other forms of
magnetism
and they were not ferrous magnetism.
That's great. It if if you want if you
want to call it non-ferrous magnetism,
that's fine. Um I I refer to it as
paramagnetic
in honor of Phil Callahan because he
while he didn't coin the term, he did do
all the major research in paramagnetism
and why it why it's beneficial for the
body. So, uh let's take a look at
magnets really quick. Um parame- uh
magnets versus paramagnetics.
Um
it's been documented over and over again
that if you take a
a south pole magnet and put it on a uh
let's say oh I I I love this one a a
little Styrofoam container of of bait
worms.
They will start to literally become
carnivorous and eat their way out of the
Styrofoam container. However, if you
flip the uh if you flip the magnet
around to the north pole side, it won't
do that. If you put live blood analysis
uh I talked about last year, dark field
microscopy. If you put a a piece of your
live blood on the on the slide and you
pass a south field magnet across it, it
will kill the blood. It will just
destroy it. That blood is is not
functional.
If you switch that magnet around and
shine and put the north pole magnet
against so that it will be beneficial to
the body. Okay? So, you have to be
careful about magnets. Paramagnetic is
not is is is completely different. It's
literally um exactly like us, so it
gives us energy.
You don't have to worry about poles.
Yes.
Can you comment on
scalar
versus paramagnetic and diamagnetic?
Um I don't quite understand what you're
saying, but I will get into the scalar
standing wave in just in just a minute,
okay? Because that interestingly enough
relates to the
relates to the Joe Cell. Okay, moving
along.
Am I making sense? Yeah. Okay, great. Um
the next thing that we come to in into
in understanding um in understanding the
Joe Cell is uh Leedskalnin's work. Now,
for those of you who are not aware,
Leedskalnin was the gentleman Edward
Leedskalnin was a gentleman who created
Coral Castle. Um he by himself, little
100-lb dude, uh moved blocks that were
in excess weighed in excess of the
largest blocks used in the Great
Pyramid. Moved them all by himself,
carved them all by himself, did
absolutely amazing things, and he wrote
a little booklet called Magnetic
Current.
It's one of the strangest books you'll
ever read. It reads like it was written
by a fourth grader.
Terrible punctuation, bad spelling. Um
it's also one of the most heavily
encoded books and one of the most
important books you could ever read in
your life because it teaches you about
magnetic resonance. This book was
written in nine in about the '40 early
'40s, right when the establishment was
changing all the books about magnetism,
okay? If you get books written before
1940 1950, you get a truer understanding
about what magnetism is. For one thing,
dowsing was an accepted science before
that time because it had to do with
magnetism.
After that, they changed the idea of
Dowsing became fringe science at best,
witchery at at worst, because they
didn't understand it anymore, okay?
So,
uh to talk about Leedskalnin,
one thing you got to understand about
Leedskalnin is he said that there are
three things in the universe, okay?
Um he said that there are three things
in the universe. There is light,
which is the neutral, there is north
poles, which is the uh which is the
positive energy, and there are south
poles, which are the negative energy.
Okay? He literally talked about um
being able to trap light, and we're
getting back to the etheric light that
that I mentioned earlier. He talked
about being able to trap a trap light,
affect the nature of reality, how he
carved those stones all by himself with
with a minimum of tools,
how to trap light and affect gravity,
which is how he moved 100,000-lb blocks
by himself without any without any
lifting apparatus,
and a number of other things that we
won't get into now.
Um the way you do it, if you if you were
to shine a light a a laser on a on a
mirror and then have another mirror over
here, you would catch the light bounce
back and forth and pretty soon that
light would get really tired and
disintegrate. Or
uh lose its energy.
Well, he said you trap light using an
infinite number of 180° planes or a
circle.
Exactly like this.
Actually, it's more like Don't bring
them up. I'll just walk over.
Actually, it's more like this. Nice and
shiny inside. We're literally trapping
etheric light utilizing the the shine
and there is a conventional scientific
establishment uh
parallel to this, by the way. It is the
uh
um
It's radiation shielding material.
I I I didn't bring it up here, but if
you can imagine a roll of toilet paper
stretched out along the ground.
Um
instead of being toilet paper, it's uh
micro-thin glass
and it is heated and then rolled
and you have literally hundreds and
hundreds of layers of this very very
thin glass and it comes back and it's
about the size of a shot glass, okay?
It's radiation shielding material.
The radiation, let's say it's this. The
radiation comes in,
goes through the glass
and goes through the spirals of the
glass until it's literally trapped in
the center
and dies.
No fuss, no muss,
no heavy lead, literally little shot
glasses,
hollow shot glasses, and that blocks
radiation.
Very interesting uh interesting
radiation shielding material. Okay, we
have got to move, so
um
Leedskalnin also gives you the uh answer
to the burning issue of positive versus
negative electricity. For those of you
um who aren't aware of the the Joe Cell
uh issue controversy right here. uh Um
they say utilizing uh negative
electricity, literally connecting the
negative pole of your alternator or your
battery to the
to the device, and then tapping it with
uh for connecting the negative pole
for a while, several minutes,
and then tapping it with the positive to
encourage the energy flow. That is
absolutely correct.
As um may not be correct in implication,
but it is correct in the fact that
negative and positive are completely
different. We are not set up to measure
one half of this. We are only set up to
measure both negative and positive flow
through the
through a wire. We are not set up to
measure the negative energy alone. So, I
have literally seen utilizing this
concept, two pieces of steel slapped
together like that with a little groove
in the center, run a wire through there,
you attach the negative energy to it,
and this is there's there's a process to
this. There's a device that will do
this, but um you attach the attach the
negative energy to it, charge those two
plates,
pop it with the positive, and those two
plates, which were
paramagnetic steel, suddenly become
neodymium magnets practically. So
powerful, a 1-in square is so powerful
that I can't pull it apart.
It'll support my weight. Who knows how
big a
you know a a uh a
20 30-in uh plate will be how powerful
that will become. Uh they're now making
safes out of this, by the way. Real cool
stuff.
Um
so
negative electricity, it's absolutely
correct. I utilize this when I utilize
my cell. Um
I I have my doubts though the whether or
not you can utilize negative electricity
utilizing a
uh an alternator.
Um
what we found is that we had to use a
battery, not a dry cell battery. We
literally had to use a wet acid battery.
Mother nature is not dry. Water is where
it's at. We literally had in order to
utilize that
that process, we could not use
generated electricity. We had to use a
We had to use a liquid source for
energy.
So,
my my contention with the Joe Cell
people, just FYI, is that you cannot
utilize a
You cannot utilize just the alternator.
You have to utilize the liquid source of
the of a battery.
So, that's and that's based on my work
and and what I do, you know, every day.
So,
moving right along, we also have
mechanical changes to water. And there
are a number of different types of ways
to mechanically change water. And what
are we doing? We're changing the
crystalline structure.
So, what we have here
is an autoclave unit.
This is my backup. I didn't bring my
real one because there's been heavy
modifications to it.
So,
this is a pressure vessel.
And as you can see,
this can handle a huge amount of
pressure. It's also shiny inside.
Oh, thank you. You're right.
Um, whoops.
Uh, it's okay. I've got it here.
Okay.
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da
da da da da Okay, mechanical
changes to water. We have pressure. We
have cold cold freezing water and then
and then bring it back to room
temperature will also change the
crystalline structure of water.
Some of the purest best water in the
entire world you can get is from the
bottom of Excuse me, from the cores of
glaciers and and icebergs that have been
very very cold Oops, sorry. Have been
very very cold for a very long time.
It's so rich in minerals that it's it's
it's life-giving just holding the bottle
for crying out loud.
Um
and I mentioned both pressure and cold
in the same right next to each other
because
there is a work being done pulling up
water, very special type of water. It's
It's It's H3. It's It's helium 3.
Pulling
water that is so rich in helium 3 out of
35,000 ft down in the ocean, very cold,
as cold as you can get with water
without freezing, and under incredibly
high pressures, more pressure than you
could possibly generate up here. Well, I
not quite, but um a hugely a huge high
pressure. And they're pulling this water
out and doing phenomenal things.
Superconductivity,
um
even
bucky tubes, um
monofilament nanowire.
They're making They're They're using
that to make that stuff. And I've
actually seen it. It's indestructible
cloth. In 10 years, we'll have clothes
you put on a pair of jeans, you'll be
wearing armor. You put on a sweater,
you'll be wearing a bulletproof shirt,
you know? It's fantastic. Um
Other ways to change water. And this is
really really important.
Um
These are vortex water devices.
The water flows in through here.
And you due to a
a slit that I cut into the plastic in
here, the water then flows in a vortex.
And the water flows in a vortex moving
around like this
until it hits this then my my my real
one fell out and that's why I had to
throw this one in there.
Um but it hits a a cone on this side and
actually reflects a certain amount of
the water back up the tube
out this end.
On this end is a is a is a cloth that
blocks um that blocks the flow of water.
If you dip this cloth into water, you
pull it out and it would be dry.
If you dip it into oil,
it just sucks it right up. So, this
cloth blocks the flow of water, but what
you get out through that Schauberger
type vortex is an oily water, which is
highly charged, highly energetic, and
this is really what you should be using
in there if you if you're so inclined.
Um theoretically, you can drink it.
I've got some right here.
Trap water. There are many different
types of traps. Um I can talk about how
to build these at the table when we get
done because apparently we're kind of
running out of time. This is my favorite
type of trap.
Oops.
That's supposed to be down there.
Water flows in through the top here,
spins in a cyclic vortex in here. Now,
remember we're all we're talking about
um
we're talking about how things move.
This literally structures water,
and you capture a certain amount of a
certain type of the water
down here in the same type of cloth that
is in the center of that in the center
of that vortex.
All of the water in there is captured as
a um
as a high-spin superconducting water.
Now, we know that it's superconducting
because one of the very interesting side
effects was
we took this thing apart and started
using it to uh distill salt out or
excuse me, evaporate salt out of
out of salt water so that we could have
nice pure salt to use.
And what we found very interestingly was
that salt was growing out of the side of
the the the stainless steel container.
Literally, salt crystals were not
climbing up and evaporating over here,
they were growing out of the side of the
stainless steel. The steel had become
superconductive, and salt was traveling
through it. All it happened all of these
things. It's uh
really amazing. We can talk about the
construction of those a little bit later
on.
So, we've got water that is um that is
no longer behaving like water. It's It's
more like an oil. Use that in your Joe
Cell sometime.
Another way to Oh, let me
change this. Did I do that? Yeah, yeah,
I got everything. All right, sound and
resonance.
And I'll show you a picture of that in a
minute. Sound and resonance is another
way to change uh to to um mechanically
change water. And when we get into that,
what we find it once again is
um we're we're coming back to a
relationship between a between Joe Cell
technology and and something else. Uh
No, it's okay, go ahead. Uh the other
one. Um
Uh
Where's my striker?
Uh-oh.
Let's see if we can do it with this.
No.
Try it on. Ah.
Okay.
I I I can't I I need wood. I apologize.
I don't have wood, but you can hear that
it is a resonance chamber. This is what
This is another thing that the Joe Cell
actually is uh operating on. Just like
Keely, who used sound and resonance to
disintegrate water down to beyond its
molecular level, beyond its atomic
structure, literally into its etheric
gas form.
We're doing the same thing
with our Joe Cells. We need to start
utilizing these as a resonance chamber
instead of just a instead just an
electrolysis chamber that we're trying
to put electricity into and get energy
out of.
Okay?
Here are some examples.
Thank you very much. Here are some
examples of some other resonance
chambers.
Keely's Dynasphere.
That's not tuned properly. That's why
it's not turning, but we'll get there
another time. That is a internal picture
of what's actually happening
is an internal picture of what's
happening inside of the uh
this
device right here.
As you can see the Schauberger vortex
that's going down the center of it.
Excuse me.
Pot trap, that is what it looks like as
it's running. If you hook that up to a
closed system, for instance, if you live
on property and you can take your well
and pump it right through that and then
catch this water and put it into a
holding tank. It's very effective. You
can get a huge amount of uh of of
effective high spin water for your for
your experiments. And I'm not talking
about just Joe Cell experiments, okay?
I'm talking about any type of
experiments. If you're working with If
you're working with Tesla coils, you can
use water. Uh you can use it as a as a
as a as a as a limiting resistor. You
can use it for all sorts of things. Um
water can can be used in in almost
anything that we're working with.
We use water We literally use certain
types of water to recharge magnets that
have died and you can recharge put put
energy back into water using water and
or excuse me, it's putting energy back
into the magnets using water in a
vortex.
Um this is a picture Believe it or not,
this is a picture of a standing wave and
I couldn't get any pictures of a any
good pictures of a standing wave in
water.
But as you can see right there, you have
a vessel which has an a closed side. You
have sound input here and sound input
here and it's literally creating a
standing wave of energy. This is the
exact same thing in a scalar wave. It's
just that instead of using water, we're
using the energy in this vacuum, okay?
Like Hartmut Müller with uh
with global scaling and I'll get to that
in in another second here. Um
the standing wave is everywhere in the
universe. If we tie in tie in with a Joe
Cell or some type of device, if we tie
into that standing wave, we can have
unlimited amount of energy. Just like
just like Hartmuller is now utilizing
this to have unlimited communication
anywhere.
Okay?
Let's go. Okay, so
I just wanted to demonstrate a few
little few little types of water. You've
all seen the shocking water. Check this
out out of the table.
This is all done with Joe Cell
technology.
This is
Excuse me, this is Ormus water. I talked
about it a little bit earlier.
This was clear until we put in certain
chemicals which allowed the
which allowed the structure to change
enough so that the Ormus material comes
out and you take two drops or or an eye
dropper full of this, put it into a
gallon of water and water your plants
with it. I had pictures last year.
Your plants will grow tremendously. It
will it will increase the yield of
anything that you put it on.
Excuse me. I'm not brave enough to drink
it. There are some people that do that
all the time. Thank you, no.
Um
This is another type of water. This is
the water that we learned how to make at
the temple site.
This is Joe Cell technology, too.
Talk to uh
Talk to Joe Blankenship about
about some of his discoveries, but that
water is literally can be literally
structured with whatever element we want
to put into it.
If you have a crystal in structure, you
change the water and make it like that.
Make it make it exactly like that. You
can taste it on your tongue. Every
single element has a distinctive flavor.
Gold has a
very To me, it's very sweet. Platinum's
kind of a
a sour flavor. Silver has another almost
citrusy flavor. Every single element has
a completely different flavor when done
when taken through a a structuring
process
with the water.
Now, nothing ever touches the water.
It's all done with energy.
But, it's all contingent upon Joe Cell
technology.
This is that water I was talking about
earlier. This is
registers on a scale of somewhere
between 11 and 14.
And
no burning, no itching, nothing.
Because it doesn't have the chemical
structure of lye, even though it's high
high uh
um even though it's high pH, it's not
going to
it's not going to burn me. It's not
going to hurt me at all. That's because
we control how it manifests in the
water. And that's all done with Joe Cell
technology.
What's that?
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought I heard
something. Oh, okay.
Sorry, I don't like my I'm I don't like
stickiness on my hands. So, anyway.
Excuse me.
Moving right along. Yes?
Oh, thank you.
Appreciate it.
Okay, let's see. Where were we? Where
were we?
Um Okay, so just to recap real quick.
We have concentric tubes of paramagnetic
steel.
We have diamagnetic spacers. And water,
of course, is paramagnetic, acting as
our vortex. Oh, drat. I was going to get
into that. Oh, man. We'll have to talk
about it at the table. I apologize. I
was going to talk about vortexes
um
um yeah, we can't get into that yet
right now. I guess we're
Um Well, I've got some more stuff to
cover here real quick. Okay. So,
we're already over on time? Okay.
Okay.
All right.
Okay. We're not over on time. Cuz if
they say we're not over Okay, great.
Good. We're not We're not over on time
yet. Okay.
Uh should we run to the table and get
something while we're not over on time?
No, it's okay. It's something to
explain. Okay.
What's interesting is if you read Phil
Callahan's work, it'll tell you about
this, but in these towers,
if you put them into water and put a
magnetic current on them with a certain
amount of
with a certain amount of minerals in
there, specifically sodium,
you will actually find that the minerals
start to manifest as a spiral
in the tower itself. Assuming on on the
tower itself. So, the literally the the
elements will naturally gravitate in a
spiral manner to specific places. Now,
one of the things that I learned just
recently on a trip to Dallas was that in
um
there are there's research now being
done utilizing spirals. You know what? I
don't need a prop. Never mind. Utilizing
spirals in an energy vacuum, they will
input high-voltage streams of electrons.
And in this vacuum, they will naturally
start to gravitate into a spiral
pattern. Okay?
The more they put in,
the more
the more those electrons stack up until
they are literally I think they found
they literally found a 14
14 distinct spirals in the pattern
before those spirals all jumped together
into a knot and another one started to
form and they would just keep on
injecting these electrons into this into
this plasma vacuum chamber and they
naturally they had no they had no
mechanism to turn it into a spiral. They
naturally formed into this spiral. What
they found was it it was incredibly
dangerous because when they reached a
critical mass, this thing had a mind of
its own and literally it shot out the
end of the tube and it would destroy
anything that came in contact with. But,
the interesting thing was that wherever
it destroyed something, it manifested
something, too.
So, um, some of you I I to some of you
about it. I I like I said, I love the
ancient connection here. All right?
They they discovered that this is a
natural phenomenon that occurs near the
pole at a very very high altitudes in
incredibly strong thunderstorms.
These lightning would manifest as a
twisted um, twisted knot that would
literally rip out of the ground and dive
into the ground and where it dove into
the ground, leave a hole as if as if a
worm, a giant fire worm had drilled into
the ground and where it came out
were precious metals. Literally
um, raw raw gemstones and precious
metals.
So, where do we get what what do we get
here? We got Ireland, we've got the
northern latitudes, we've got the pot of
gold at the end of the rainbow. We've
got the fire worms coming out of the
ground. Um, you know, if if you watch
the watch the movie The 13th Warrior,
remember that was a true story. They
literally expected to be going out and
fighting dragons
because they were in the northern
latitudes, these things were fairly
common in these in these areas that they
had massive thunderstorms.
Okay?
Um,
going back to So, so we're talking about
making metals here and I I want to talk
about this, too. Great. Thank you. I I I
completely did forget to touch on this.
Um, two friends in Dallas
um, they took Joe Cell type device. As a
matter of fact, it was almost exactly
like this one right here. So, good job.
Um,
they loaded it up with water, but they
wanted to see what would happen if they
put in heavy minerals. So, they had a
very set amount of water that they put
in and then they added very heavy
concentration of a liquid minerals into
this into the cell.
And then they just put on as much
voltage as they could handle without
overloading their power supply. And of
course, they're bubbling hydrogen off
and they're making all this this scum on
top of the water and they've got a whole
lot of minerals and pretty soon all
pretty soon minerals start to drop out
and short out the short out the power
supply down here at the bottom of the
short out the power supply because it's
so congested down here.
Well, they're catching all of this
hydrogen and oxygen. They're catching it
all
and they recombine it back into water,
okay? Scrape off the minerals, drain out
this gunk at the bottom of this thing,
put the water back in and start all over
again.
And what they found was that they ended
up with the using TDS meters, they found
that they ended up with the exact same
amount of minerals in the water
that they started with.
But they got minerals out here that they
just skimmed off the top and drained out
the bottom, okay?
And so they did it all over again. Boil
water or excuse me
boil the hydrogen and oxygen off.
Got a whole bunch of scum up there. The
thing shorts out because there's a whole
bunch of deposits down here. They drain
it all out, sift it all out, pour the
water back in.
They got the exact same amount of
minerals that they started with
and now they got twice as much out here.
And they do it all over again. And they
do it all over again and they do it 13
times. 13 times the amount of minerals
using the exact same water, the exact
same uh
the exact same amount of minerals to
start with each time and they just quit
because they got bored. They manifested
they created 13 times the amount of
minerals that they started with.
So Einstein's equation, Einsteinian
physics says we can take a small amount
of matter, little tiny amount of matter
or a you know, something like this like
a bomb
and we can create a huge amount of
energy from it. But Einsteinian physics
says that it takes just that same amount
of energy to put it back in and to make
a tiny amount of matter.
But etheric physics that uh
quantum physics, etheric physics trumps
Einsteinian physics and suddenly we have
a an example of a very tiny amount of
energy relatively, a very tiny amount of
energy going in and literally making
matter from energy, but it has to be in
the proper
configuration. It has to be in the
proper way. So, that's how
I can make this stuff
and somebody uh
goes and they they they put they add a
chlorine to it and a couple of
chemicals. I'm not a chemist, so I I
don't know exactly what he did, and he
gets gold chloride, and he's getting it
from the water, and yet
I didn't lose anything making it
except water.
Okay? And a little bit of energy.
That's why um
excuse me. That is a possible
explanation. I'm not saying that this is
what's going on, but that is a possible
explanation why the Joe Cell is
generating
more than what you're putting into it,
because you've stored energy into it,
and you're getting hydrogen out to run
your vehicle.
Um
don't know. Like I said, never seen a
Joe Cell work on a car, but I use a Joe
Cell every day to charge water, and I've
seen that I get a whole lot more energy
out than what I put in. Don't ask me to
generate to to make a to make a an an
an electrical generator, that's not my
deal, okay?
Um
but it has to be in the right
configuration. It has to be in the right
um
in the right state, otherwise it won't
function properly. Okay, real quick, I
want to um
tell you a little bit more about what's
being done. Like I said, we charge water
with etheric energy using Joe Cell
technology.
Let's see, what was the next slide?
Okay. Um
we we imprint water with a signature
with signatures of an element, and it
behaves as if it's the element.
We also create superconducting
materials. There's a gentleman now that
uses this exact same site same type of
stuff, runs it through a process, plates
it onto uh electrical wire, and it
becomes a superconductor, 0.000008
ohms, okay? And he can wrap it into a
coil, pulse it with 1 V of electricity,
and out comes 1.3 V.
Unfortunately, he's in bed with the DOE,
so you know, we'll never see that one.
But,
there are many things that you can do
with uh with with water and with
specifically structured water. Now,
we're working with a uh there's an
organization called um
Tesla Communications International,
and it uses water in a vessel,
and what happens is we put a specific
specific amount of of of structured
energized water
with a specific amount of Ormus elements
to increase the conductivity, and it
behaves like an antenna. We've got its
range a smaller one than this. We've got
its range up to 25 mi now,
broadcasting a ham radio, and we're
getting better reception and using less
power than an overhead radio or overhead
antenna.
So, the applications for this are
absolutely tremendous. I want to read
something here at the very end of this
presentation. Okay, so anyway,
if you're using it to run a car, or
you're trying to use it to run trying to
use Joe Cell technology to run a car,
I don't know if there will be any
success with it
in the northern hemisphere, in the
southern hemisphere. I don't know if
there's going to be any success with it,
okay? I'm not here to tell you that. I'm
here to tell you that um the Joe Cell
technology is a tip of the iceberg when
it comes to these future when it comes
to our future, okay? We have a device
that is being that is accepted as being
a device that is contingent upon the
mindset of the user,
okay? It's contingent upon how the
person thinks and acts and behaves. So,
that is the most important We're moving
into a new generation here. We're moving
into a new uh a new technology and this
is paving the way for it. So everyone
that's working on it with a car,
you know, that's fantastic. Remember
that you are that you are paving the way
for something more in the future. And if
you if anyone in here has said, "Wow, I
am excited about this. This is really
neat. I want to try maybe that
communications thing or I want to try
the resonance thing or I want to do
something else with the Joe Cell."
That's really what I'm here to to talk
about because this is this is to kind of
teach you the the foundation and I and
we're moving ahead, too.
What we need to do is we need to take
all this information, everything that
we've everything that I've talked about
today, everything that you know about
Tesla and Schauberger and Keely, put it
all together in a whole and say, "Where
am I going to take the technology?"
What we need to do is find a new way of
utilizing this power, okay? We can we
can put it into a into a motor.
But honestly, that is like literally
taking the the anti-matter warp core of
the starship enterprise and trying to
run a run a technology on it that has
not changed significantly in a hundred
years.
Okay? That's next generation technology
our next generation power going
backwards a hundred years to technology.
You might make it work, but it's going
to be a whole lot of hassle.
Instead, what I propose is that we find
a new concept for utilizing this, okay?
And I want to I want to read something.
This is a quote from my friend John
DePew.
Drats, I didn't even just talk about
that.
Um
He's got the Holy Grail.
Okay?
Go to coralcastlecode.com.
Um as a matter of fact, let's let's
scroll into the references here real
quick. Um
Let's this is one set of references.
Copy those down. That's very important.
Uh let me read this while you're copying
that down.
This knowledge was first revealed in our
ancient past, then suppressed again
until people like John W. Keely, Walter
Russell, Nikola Tesla, Ed Leedskalnin,
and on and on tried to share it with us.
And now here it is again, revealed again
in our time. So, please pay attention
here. The truth has been revealed. Now,
teach your children and loved ones the
truth so that they may have a bright and
fruitful future. If we are wise, we
won't forget or lose or ignore it this
time. Good luck to all of you who have
participated and who will in the future.
Once again, thank you very much to
everyone who is involved. Okay?
Work on it. Move forward in it. Does
everybody have this written down? No.
Okay.
Yes, sir. One of those URLs is
misspelled.
I'm sorry. Which one? Orgonite is o r g
o n i t e. I excuse me. I'm sorry. It's
o r g o n i t e and I don't know where
that goes. So, don't trust what happens.
Apologize for that one. No problem.
Yes, sir.
Apologize for that one. No, don't click
on it.
I told you not to click on that.
Oh, okay. Good. We're all right.
Deutschland? Okay. Anyway,
let's let's go back real quick. I want
to explain each one of those links,
okay?
Okay. subtleenergies.com,
the most comprehensive and extensive
library of ORMUS high-spin high-energy
elements of information on high-spin
high-energy elements that there are.
Uh orgonite,
o,
talks about uh cloudbuster technology.
Please visit that.
magnetricity
Um
John Mallus key, superluminal light
theory
uh talks about how we need to move away
from elec- electromagnetism and move to
magnoelectricity,
okay? Magnetricity is a really
phenomenal site for information on on
electricity and magnetism. This is
sympathetic vibratory physics. This is
a Dale Pond site on John Keely. If
anyone hasn't visited that one, please
go there. neilslaid.com
That's That's one of my favorites. That
is a really fun and interesting site
really fun and interesting information
from the whole brain research institute,
a foundation established back in the
1960s teaching people how to control
their thoughts and move out of a um
move out of a reptilian survival fight
or flight mindset, move beyond just the
mammalian I'm going to nest and protect
my home, move into your frontal lobe
type of thoughts. They teach you how to
how to how to think beyond the box,
thinking creativity create creative
thoughts. They are not some type of
anecdotal fun stuff. They're little
exercises that teach you how to control
your mind, okay? And once you can
control your mind, one way you can
control it the other way. So, once you
can live in your frontal lobes, you can
then move back into your reptilian mode
and your your instincts are completely
honed. Excuse me, your instincts are
honed and you have extrasensory
awareness, all sorts of fun stuff. Uh
Leedskalnin is a group out of Australia,
leedskalnin.com.
They have actually uh found a way to um
uh utilize his techniques and actually
demonstrate how magnetic fields and how
electrical current flows in
in wire and and just in nature.
coralcastlecode.com
um
Everybody go there and email him and
tell him that he needs to come here next
year, okay?
This guy has the holy grail of free
energy.
I've seen it. It is one of the most It
was one of the coolest free energy
devices I have ever seen, the only one
that I've ever seen that that I could
actually say yes, that's there it is.
It's spinning magnets.
Can't talk too much about it, but
literally
got a set of spinning magnets here
at a certain ratio which actually fits
with the Phi harmonics. At a certain
ratio, you have another set of spinning
magnets here.
Oh, this one's drawing a certain amount
of power. This one is spun by that one,
and then you've got another one and
another one and another one and another
one. And I personally have seen 60 sets
of spinning magnets all going at the
same time, never drawing more power than
the one over here because all of those
are tied in using the magnetic fields,
the vortexes
of magnet elect energy
traveling through the universe. So,
it'll work right here, but it won't work
2 in over, interestingly enough.
Um
so, it's literally mapping the magnetic
fields that we move in every single day.
Go to this site. It's phenomenal stuff.
Once you figured Once you figure out the
code, then you get into a an even deeper
site, and that's pretty cool. That's
that's even more amazing. So,
um email him tell him he needs to come
here. He cannot give this technology
away. It's disgusting. He has It doesn't
matter how big these magnets are. As
long as you can spin them to the
resonant speed of the first set of
magnets, they will spin.
Okay?
And he can't give it away. He's called
physicists, he's called electricians,
he's called electrical engineers. No one
wants it.
Okay? It's a technique to travel the
universe and all sorts of fun stuff. I I
just one more second here. Here's the
next set of references.
Actually, I have magnetricity twice.
That was supposed to be Mueller power up
there.
Um company I'm working with at this
point. The very last page of the
internet, visit this and download this
movie.
Jerry Smith movie. It's Jerry Smith
movies.
Um it will teach you how magnetic fields
work. Magnetic fields do not look like
you you you uh when you stick a magnet
with a bunch of iron filings and just
you can't download it. It's it's it's
down right now for some reason and it's
it's a movie so it takes a long time.
But anyway, um
go there because it will completely
change your view of magnetism. Magnets
do not move like that like like like
like they show in an iron filing. That's
what magnets stacked on top of each
other look like. Moving magnets, magnets
are constantly in motion. Magnets are
constantly in a spiral motion. Okay?
Magnets are literally free energy and if
we knew how to and if we could actually
see that as you will see in this movie,
you will see you'll start to see ways to
generate energy just using a magnet
sitting there. Okay?
Um Masaru Emoto, I think I got that one
right. Um
messages from water, we talk about the
emotional content of your thoughts going
into water. Your emotional contents go
into your thoughts and your body because
you're 90% water. So you better start
learning how to control your thoughts.
Go back to neilslade.com. John
Malluskey, super luminous light theory.
Light as comes out of black holes
permeates into our sun, permeates into
our our skies, energizes our body. Uh
Phil Callahan, by paramagnetism like I
said one of the most intelligent men
that there is. Unfortunately, he can't
remember it now.
So
um
Alex Schiffer, if you want to study Joe
Cell, that's the starting place the
book. Uh I don't think I spelled that
right.
And Karl von Reichenbach talks about how
etheric energy flows and it draws energy
in through various um
paramagnetic, diamagnetic, natural,
synthetic materials.
All right?
Thank you very much everybody. I
appreciate you letting me go over.
Ladies and gentlemen, Vernon Roth. Thank
you very much, Vernon.
Mhm.